《致命弯道2：死路》
喂?
Hello?
我要死在外面了 我恨死你了
It's dead out here, and I'm hating you about now.
你算哪门子经纪人? 你会找到那条路的
What kind of agent are you? You'll fnd the road.
Kimberly 洛杉机这边才凌晨四点 你还让不让人睡?
Kimberly, look, it's 4:00 a.m. in L.A. Can I go back to sleep?
你还骗我说是头等舱 害我整晚没合眼
I was up all night on the red-eye, and it wasn't frst class like you promised.
我好歹也给你弄了台好车吧? 好啦好啦
Give me credit for the car. Nice ride, huh? Yeah, whatever.
还有 这些指示图很烂 这个节目也烂
By the way, these directions suck. This project sucks.
K 这是一次难得的机会 这不过是真人秀节目的首播
K., it's a great opportunity. It's a reality show pilot.
打上次上镜以来 你就高歌猛进至前七
You sang your way to the top seven the last time you were on TV.
你现在是明星了 你是强大的Kimberly Caldwell
Now you're the star. You're Kimberly fucking-Caldwell.
你是他们手上唯一的明星
You're the only celebrity they've got.
我要真那么大牌 Tommy 你就给我签部电影回来
If I'm such a celebrity, Tommy, get me a movie.
"Kimster" 你将因此而人气飚升 你将有机会赢得九万元奖金
''Kimster'', your Q score's gonna go way up, and you'll have a chance to win 90 grand.
不是十万吗? 我提成10% 不记得了?
I thought it was a hundred. Well, I get 10%, remember?
等等 有个岔路口
Wait. There's a turnoff.
我睡前差不多练了两小时力量瑜珈 累死了
Look, I've got power yoga in, like, two hours.
你还没找到吗? 我不知道 有间老造纸厂在这
Did you fnd it yet? I don't know. There's some old paper mill here.
但地图上没写 没错 那就对了
But there's nothin' about it on the map. Yeah. That's gotta be it.
Kimbo 你绝对不能走错 你没时间了
Look, ''Kimbo,'' you can't afford to make a wrong turn here. You really don't have the time.
我为什么要来这里? 因为这一行竞争激烈
Why am I here? 'Cause this business is tough.
你信号不好 我所有的委托人中 惟独你…
You're breaking up. Of all my clients,you're the one...
喂? 喂? 有这种…
Hello? Hello? with the factor here-
操
Fuck!
天啊天啊天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
不要死 不要死啊
Don't be dead. Don't be dead.
救命 救命啊
Help! Help!
该死
Shit!
有人吗
Anybody!
没事的 我会找人来救你
Don't worry. I'm gonna get you help, okay?
不 不 求你 不要死
No! No, please! Please! No, don't die!
振作 呼吸 呼吸
Come on! Breathe! Breathe!
我在这里 我在这里
I'm here. I'm here.
世界末日来了
It's the end of the world...
社会动荡 政府不再控制局面
society in chaos, governments no longer in control.
灾害肆虐 世界千疮百孔 而你仍然存活于世
The world has been devastated by a catastrophic disaster, but you're still alive.
一夜之间 你被抛回蛮荒时代
Overnight, you've been thrust back into the Stone Age.
现代社会的便利已为过去式
Modern conveniences are a thing of the past.
你还有求存的勇气吗?
Would you have the guts to survive?
我是退伍海军上校Dale Murphy
I am retired Marine Colonel Dale Murphy.
欢迎来到"末日启示录"
Welcome to The Apocalypse.
在接下来的五天里 六位参赛者…
Over the next fve days, these six contestants...
将接受终极考验
will be put to the ultimate test.
我将会是最终的生还者…
I'm gonna be the ultimate survivor...
因为上次节目让我明白 不计一切取胜才是王道
because on my last show I learned more than anything what it takes to win.
这纹身代表什么?
So what's the tattoo?
它象征"永恒" 因为我要被载入史册
It's the ''infnity'' sign, because I wanna be remembered forever.
大家都叫我"Jonesy"
My friends call me ''Jonesy''...
但"无所畏惧"是我的另一个名字
but ''Fearless'' is my middle name.
这是错误示范 兄弟
Ow! That sucked, dude.
不是叫你修补跑道吗 可以重来吗?
I told you to shave that ride. Can we do that again?
大家好 我是Elena
Hi. I'm Elena.
我就像狐狸 性感 狡猾…
I'm like a fox sexy, sleek...
而且我总能得到自己想要的
and I always get what I want.
Nina 我是个幸存者…
Nina. I'm a survivor...
因为我知道只有一个人靠得住那就是自己
because I know there's only one person I can count on myself.
我是Jake 肌腱套上的三次手术…
I'm Jake. Three surgeries on my rotator cuff...
使我和职业橄榄球生涯擦肩而过
destroyed my shot at a pro football career-
但这不能阻止我夺魁
but not my drive to win.
Amber 在伊拉克服役一期 他们称我为"征服者"
Amber. One tour of duty in Iraq. They call me ''La Conquistadora. ''
废话少说 誓死效忠
Enough said. Semper fi,
六名参赛者将被一同流放至荒野
These six contestants have been thrown together in a devastated wasteland...
随身物品只有身上的衣服 还有求生欲望
with only the clothes on their backs...and the will to survive.
无论晴空万里还是雷雨大作 五天内只有一人留下
Rain or shine, in fve days, only one will remain.
欢迎来到"末日启示录"
Welcome to The Apocalypse.
你看怎么样?
Well, what do you think, man?
我们花了一整晚剪辑
We spent all last night cutting it.
Brando 还是你行 你才居功至伟 Dale
Brando, eat your heart out. You're the real deal, Dale.
这就是行内人喜欢你的原因
That's why the network loves you.
太棒了 M 还用你说
It rocks, M Damn straight.
节目一定能做下去
We're goin' to series for sure.
下地狱的好日子 制片人哪去了?
Ah! Today's a good day to die. Where's my producer?
太妙了 Michael 我说真的 过奖
It's brilliant, Michael. Really. Thank you.
我还是觉得这和别的 生存节目没什么不同
I still don't see what makes this show any different from that other survivor show.
我不看电视
I don't watch television.
这是发生在世界末日的 这就是不同
It's supposed to take place at the end of the world. That's what makes it different.
你们不是来什么避暑圣地 结识朋友的
You're not on some summer resort trying to make alliances.
你们的目标 是在"末日启示录"中笑到最后
You're trying to be the last man standing after the apocalypse.
很吃香 中美家庭娱乐节目
It's killer Middle America family entertainment, mate. Booyah.
一点没错 我去定了 伙计
That's damn right. I'm so there, dude.
少来 我正打算成为唯一坚持到底的女性
No. I plan on being the last woman standing.
切 "Ramba"(印度女演员) 奖金非我莫属
Chill, ''Ramba.'' The prize money's gonna be mine.
两位美女不如在泥池里摔交决定吧
Oh, you two girIs could mud wrestle for it.
一决高下
Be ratings gold. Ew.
你真逊 我在泡她
You're stupid, man. I am tappin' that.
这不是花鹦鹉吗 衣服真花哨
Hey, it's the parrot heads. Nice shirts, boys.
尽管取笑好了
Yeah, make fun all you want.
当你们这些好莱坞怪胎 在石头上睡觉时
But while you Hollywood freaks are out here sleepin' on rocks...
我们这些花鹦鹉就住海边酒店 享受美酒和沙滩
us parrot heads will be in Margaritaville back at the hotel.
树上线都搭好了 32台摄象机和麦已经准备好了
The woods are all wired up 3 2 cameras and mikes ready to go.
你真够意思Wojo 要保证每样东西都符合Neil要求
Oh, you the man, Wojo.Just make sure everything's copacetic with Neil, okay?
五天后见 好好享受户外生活 Tarantino
Yeah. See ya in fve days. Enjoy the great outdoors, Tarantino.
很好
Nice.
我可以帮你擦你够不着的地方
I could help you spread it on all those hard-to-reach places.
要不是我看见你去年六月…
If I hadn't seen you eat shit at the X Games lastJune, maybe you'd stand a chance.
在极限运动中摔了个狗吃屎 你还是有机会的
我可是闯入了决赛哦
Hey, I made the street comp fnals.
给你个提示 我只对冠军有兴趣
Okay. Here's a clue. I only give it up to winners-
而不是你这个倒胃口的家伙
not guys who choke.
我就叫你倒胃口
I'll give you something to choke on.
我有你那么健美就好了
I wish I had abs like yours.
我每天做200下
I do 200 of these a day.
那我还是继续吃健康餐好了
I guess I'll just stick to my low-carb diet and hope for the best.
Mara Kimberly哪去了? 仍不知道
Mara, where the hell's Kimberly? Still no answer.
他妈的 我就知道请这风头正劲 的歌星迟早出岔子
Goddamn it. I knew that prima donna was a problem when we cast her.
没错 但她的嘴唇 很像安吉利娜 茱莉
Yeah, but she's got those Angelina Jolie lips.
你懂我意思吧?
You know what I'm talkin' about, don't you?
乖乖…漫长的五天啊
Hello, papa. It's gonna be a long fve days.
不能再等了 我要马上开拍了
We can't wait any longer. I gotta shoot, like, now.
你是制片人 内柔外刚 所以说你能赚钱
You're the producer, Pop-Tart. That's why you make the big bucks.
我们该怎么做? 我们不可能再找人
What are we gonna do? Um, well, we can't recast.
所以只能五个人照拍了 不 这不行
We're just gonna have to go with fve. Whoa, whoa. No, wrong.
你知道这节目的 我给你拍个选手介绍就可以了
You know the show. All I have to do is shoot your character intro, and we're good to go.
不 不行 还有什么好建议?
No, I don't think so. What other choice do we have?
好吧 真该死
Um. Okay, yeah. What the hell?
就这么办 给他们看看你的厉害
That's it! Show 'em what you're made of.
好的各位 听好了
All right, boys and girls, listen up!
我们要徒步半英里去营地
We have a half-mile hike to the survivalist camp.
走吧 该出发了
Let's go! It's time to move out!
好的 大家带上家伙出发
All right. Everybody grab your gear, and let's get going.
就这么多 Michael
This is it. Hey, Michael.
没有"黑莓"商务通和手机 我就束手无策
You know I'm a complete geek without my BlackBerry and my cell.
我很有可能第一个淘汰
There's a good chance I'll be the frst to go.
别这样 换上衣服 涂上驱虫剂
Come on.Just change your clothes, put on some bug spray.
你会很出色 就算没有你的"发霉"商务通
You'll be great, even without your ''CrackBerry.''
好吧 给你面子
Okay. I'll do it for you.
但是从现在开始…Mara
But, um, now, Mara.
叫我M 别叫Michael
It's M now, not Michael.
知道了 对不起 好
Yes, I know. Okay. Sorry. Right.
天 自寻烦恼
God, who am I kidding?
好的 我们出发
Okay. We're movin' out.
在外面你们将孤立无援 因此我们尽量保持队型不要走散
You're all alone out here, so let's close ranks and stick together.
大家都走了
Hey, everyone's leavin'
听见吗? 大伙都走了
Hello? Hey. Everyone's leaving.
什么? 比赛要开始了 该出发了
What? We're about to start the game. It's time to go.
你好 我是Jake 你是Nina对吧?
Hi. I'm Jake. You're Nina, right?
听着 我来这里是为了钱 不是交朋友 懂吗?
Look, I'm just here for the money, not to make friends, okay?
好 随便你
Wow. Okay. Fair enough.
Nina Nina…
ff Oh. Nina. Nina.
刚才你下车时掉了这个
I saw you drop this while you were getting out of the R.V.
M说了不准带食物 我是素食主义
Now, M said, ''No food.'' Oh, well, I'm vegan.
在这边我只能吃这个了
That might be the only thing I can eat out here.
但你可以随时到树上摘果子吃 这是作弊
Well, you can always go chew on a tree. This is cheating.
告发我嘛 拿来
Sue me. Give it back. Uh-uh.
本来我想给你的 但是…你说不是来这交朋友的
I would have, but...since there's no need to be makin' friends-
一级棒
That's good.
大伙准备好了吗?
All right, everybody. Ready?
开拍 Dale
And action, Dale.
你无法凭一己之力存活
You cannot survive the apocalypse alone.
因此你要建立关系 与盟友共同攻关
So you make friendships, perform tasks together.
你需要判断谁能与你共渡难关 以及谁将被大家淘汰
You fgure out who you need to ride out the chaos and who's expendable.
今天我们将被分为三组 进树林里寻找食物
Today, we're gonna split into three teams, go out and search for food.
你们每人挑选的号码 代表各自的队友
The number each of you picked decides your teammate.
我总是第一 宝贝
Number one all the way, baby..
你和我一组 宝贝 路上多关照
You and me, baby. All the way.
谁是2号? 我刚在加油站后面拉了泡屎(2号有大便意思)
Who's got a number 2? I did a number two back at the gas station.
笑笑嘛 太不给面子了
Come on, dude. That was funny.
真棒
Oh, sweet.
貌似我们俩一组 哎?
I guess you and me are a team. Hello?
年轻人们 这是世界末日
All right, boys and girls, it's the end of the world...
一开始你们就会困难重重
and the odds are against you from the start.
核污染已为事实
Radiation poisoning is a reality.
所以你们身上要戴着这个
That's why you're all wearing these.
每天每人会得到一张辐射消除卡
Every day,you'll be given a radiation elimination card.
而当中的一张是带有辐射的
And one of them is already contaminated.
到了晚上持有该卡的选手将出局
At the end of the day, the player holding the simulated radiated card is dead.
别担心 这只是说明你不及格
Don't worry. It just means you're disqualified.
但你有机会通过把卡 转移给他人而复活
But you have a chance to survive the day by giving your card to another player...
并成功消除辐射
and surviving the radiation elimination.
这是对意志力 忍耐力 和运气的考验
It's a test of your personal will, your endurance and fate.
在"末日" 你的命运可以像这样改变
And in The Apocalypse, your fate can change like that.
野生动物 细菌感染 后末日狂热
Wild animals, bacterial infection and post-apocalyptic crazies...
都在你身边虎视耽耽
are all around you, waiting to take you down.
他们能被这个…监测到
They're represented...by these.
我们称它为"命运的扭曲"
We call them ''Twists'' of Fate.
它们是生存挑战 多多少少的…
They are survival challenges, and dozens of them...
散布在比赛区域
are scattered all over the playing area.
要是触发了传感器 就会听到…
You trigger the motion sensor, and you hear this-
背面的信息阐述了你们的挑战内容
lnstructions on the back explain your survival challenge.
完成挑战 你就…
Accomplish the challenge, and you earn the right...
可取得辐射卡并交给你选择的选手
to take your radiated card and give it to any player you choose...
并安全度过今天
and automatically survive the day.
下午六点此处集合 谁被淘汰到时分晓
We are going to assemble back here at 1800 hours and see who will perish in the chaos...
看看谁离十万奖金更进一步
and who is one step closer to $100,000.
祝你们好运 切记…
Good luck to all of you. Remember-
团队精神是生还的关键
You have to work as a team to survive the game.
但只有一人…
But only one of you can be the ultimate survivalist...
能在"末日"之后生还
after the apocalypse.
停 漂亮 Dale 好
And cut! Nice work, Dale. All right!
我准备好吊足观众的胃口了 大导演
I'm ready for my 15 minutes, Hollywood.
好的 大家
Okay, everybody.
音频视频正通过耳机传送回编辑部
Uh, the headsets are transmitting audio and video back to the edit bay, so-
所以先别摘下来 还有…
So don't take them off. And, also, uh-
手机和PDA等等都交给Neil
Cell phones and P.D.A.'s, etcetera give 'em to Neil.
他会把他们放进卡车里
He's gonna put them in the R.V.
玩开心点 我去撒泡尿了 去吧
Have fun. I got to go take a wicked piss, mate. Mm-hmm.
按原计划我会先跟着Elena和Jake
Okay. I'm gonna follow Elena and Jake frst, as planned.
大家记住要真实展现
Uh,just remember, everybody Let's make it feel real.
好的
Okay.
嘿 怎么了? 我肯定会出丑
Hey. What's up? I'm so gonna suck at this.
我当初为什么会听你的?
Why'd I let you talk me into it?
因为我魅力无法挡?
Mmm, because I'm irresistible?
你个大坏蛋 走了
You're a jerk, you know? Gotta go.
上校 要是消除辐射的环节 输了会怎样?
Colonel...What happens if we lose the elimination round?
你会回旅行车里 到我和Jack Daniel这黯自伤心…
We go back to the R.V., and you drown your sorrows with me and Jack Daniel's...
直至比赛结束 听起来很有意思
until the game is done. Oh, that sounds like fun.
但别担心 甜心 我会罩着你的
But don't worry, sweetness. I won't let you lose.
要是有该死的猪头山里人敢乱来 我会保护你的
And if any of those pig-fuckin' hillbillies come around, I got your back.
嘿 蠢货 我就是在这附近长大的
Hey, bonehead! I grew up two counties from here!
我还从没跟猪上过床
I never had sex with a pig in my life!
你是歧视乡下人吗?
You're not promotin' stereotypes, are you, son?
放机灵点
Outstanding!
这里的人脾气也许没我那么好 管好你的臭嘴
People in these parts might not take that talk too well! You might wanna put a lid on it!
有没问题 "星爷"? 没…没问题
Is that all right with you, funnyman? Ye-Yes, sir.
够…够酷
Uh Th-Th-That's cool.
你们之间有那种"军人情结"
You guys got the whole ''military bond'' thing happenin'.
誓死效忠之类的废话 没错
Semper fi and shit. Yeah.
而且我们都讨厌人渣
And we both hate assholes.
靠技师临走前该把这些都安置好
Shit. The techies were supposed to fnish setting these up before they left.
丢掉制片人的身份 专心投入比赛
Put your producer hat away and get your head in the game.
这些交给我 正好我闲着
I'll set these up. I got time to kill anyway.
谢谢 我也不想操这个心
Thank you. God, I wish I didn't have to do this.
小Mikey真把你给拉下水了
Old Mikey really put you on the spot, didn't he?
我猜他是觉得把一个城市女孩 丢进大森林里会很有噱头
I guess he thinks it'll be entertaining to send a city girl into the woods.
我倒觉得很残酷 但别担心
Cruel if you ask me, but don't worry.
你身上有些特质他没有发现 而我发现了
There's something in you he doesn't see that I do.
你也许很漂亮 但你比你想象中更坚强
You may be pretty, but you're tougher than you think.
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
"Neen"我们该往哪…
So, ''Neen,'' which way should we-
看来该往那走
I guess we go that way.
你要是吃鱼 也许该往河边走
If you eat fish, maybe we should head towards the river to find some food.
我吃素的 我不吃不用任何动物产品
I'm vegan. I don't eat or use any animal products...
包括水里游的
including the swimming kind.
可你的裤带 似乎是皮制的
Oh. Isn't your beIt made of leather?
是仿皮 我不是伪君子
It's pleather. I'm not a hypocrite.
不 我不是这意思
No, I didn't think that you were.
正因为你是素食主义者 才会被挑来上节目
Being vegan is why you got picked to be on the show.
M 觉得对你来说这外面没什么可吃
M. thought there wouldn't be a lot for you to eat out here...
你说不定得被迫吃幼虫撑肚子
and you might have to resort to gulping down insect larva or something.
美国人看真人秀不就是 喜欢这些恶心东西吗?
It's the kind of thing America loves in its reality shows, right?
美国很变态 不假
America's sick. Yeah.
我讨厌真人秀 都是些弱智节目
I hate reality shows. They're pretty idiotic.
那你为什么要做? 本职工作
Then why are you doing this? Because it's my job.
这是M的第一个企划 我需要表示下支持
It's M's frst project, and I'm just trying to be supportive.
我要是他女朋友 我直接讲:"破点子 你自己疯去"
If I was his girlfriend, I would've said, ''This sucks. You're on your own.''
不 我不信 我当然会
Come on. No, you wouldn't. Yeah, I would.
你也许没注意到 我其实挺贱的
If you haven't noticed, I can be a bit of a bitch.
要是你那么讨厌真人秀 你又为什么要来?
Well, if you hate reality shows, then why are you doing this?
走你的路就是了 要找些吃的
Let's just keep going. We've gotta fnd some food.
他妈的捣蛋鬼
Fucking weekend warriors.
你最好到此为止 不然就叫你好看
You'd better stand down, or someone's gonna get hurt!
断箭 打猎一定用得上
Broken arrow. That's really gonna help us hunt for food.
矛 我喜欢 又长又硬
A spear. I like it. It's so long and hard.
开玩笑
I'm just goofn'.
我在车里看了你的简历
Come on. I l read your bio back in the R. V.
西点军校 平均分4.0 你既有脑 又很强壮
West Point, 4.0 average. You're brainy. That's tight.
你一定爱看书吧 你最喜欢哪本书?
I, uh, bet you're a reader. What's your favorite book? Huh?
我非常喜欢"戴帽子的猫" (小孩子看的童话书)
I'm into Cat in the Hat myself.
你那句"在伊拉克服役一期"很酷
You did the whole ''tour of duty in Iraq'' thing. That's cool.
我虽然反战 但我也接受你这样的爱国者
I'm more of a pacifst myself, but, hey, I can get down with the patriotism.
制服诱惑 闭嘴行吗?
Woman in uniform's a turn-on. Will you shut up?
噢 她开口了 嘘
Oh. She talks. Shh!
我们走了三小时…
We've been hiking for three hours...
却从未发现过任何虫鱼鸟兽
but we haven't seen or heard any animaIs or birds.
一片死寂
It's dead quiet out here.
很恐怖 不是吗? 只剩我俩孤男寡女
It's freaky, right? It's like we're all alone.
我们想怎么干都行 没人知道 除了三千万观众
We could get all nasty, and nobody'd see a thing except for 30 million people.
别装了 你难道一点不心动吗?
Come on. You're into me, like, a little bit.
你还不懂吗? 我不喜欢男人
You just don't get it, do you? I'm not into men.
你是拉拉?
You-You're a lesbian?
好性感
How hot is that?
好的 让我把焦距调好
All right. Let mejust get it focused here.
开始
And action.
我在二号位 然后一号位
So I'm at the two. I'm at the one.
我跳起 飞跃 砰
I jump. I leap. Bam!
肩膀就变型了
Shoulder was never the same.
成为职业球员的唯一机会 就这么没了
Killed my chances at a pro career just like that.
很可笑
It's funny.
因为你不知道命运何时会改变
'Cause you never know when your life's gonna change.
天啊我打六岁起就梦想着 参加美国橄榄球大联盟
Man, I wanted to be in the NFL so bad since I was 6.
亲爱的 我完全理解你的处境
Oh, honey, I totally understand where you're coming from.
不 老兄 别看镜头 看她
No. Dude, don't Don't look in the lens. Look at-
那么大学毕业后你就这么 无所事事地寻找自我吗?
So, um, then, after college, you just bounced around tryin' to fnd yourself?
是啊直到这次节目为止 我的机会来了
Yeah, well, this opportunity came up, you know, to be on this TV show.
我打不了橄榄球了 但我仍有运动细胞
I can't throw a football no more, but I'm still athletic.
上天赐予的好身体不用白不用
Mm-hmm. I fgure I'll use the talents that God gave me, right?
我们待会再好好谢谢上天
Well, we'll have to thank God later.
没错 待会好好谢它
Yeah, right. Thank God later.
我好象听到那边有河水声
You know, I I think I hear the river this way. Yeah.
来
Come on.
老天是不是忘了赐你小弟弟了?
God didn't give you a pair of balls?
休息一下吧?
How about we take a break?
我们要找到食物 如果我们证明了我们是最好的…
We have to fnd food. If we prove that we're the best at it...
大家把辐射卡给我们的机率就比较小
then it's less likely anybody will give us their radiation card.
我没看见什么可吃的
I haven't seen anything to eat.
他奶奶的
Ow! Holy shit!
是"命运扭曲" 我触发它了
It's one of those Twist of Fates. I set it off.
在哪里?
Where is it?
你们已被附近实验室爆炸释放的 炭疽所感染
''You've been infected by anthrax from a nearby laboratory explosion.
解药可在河边找到 你有两分钟
An antidote can be found by the river. You have two minutes.''
天啊找得到才怪 是啊好运 走吧
God, I would get this. Yeah, well, good luck. Go.
跟过来 你得拍到我才行
Hey, come and shoot. We need your footage.
我好象看见河了 哪里?
I think I see the river! Where?
现在要怎么做? 看那个
What do you need now? That!
"还有一分钟"
One minute remaining.
"45秒"
Forty-five seconds remaining.
"30秒"
Thirty seconds remaining.
8 7…
Eight, seven...
6 5…
six, fve...
4 3 2…
four, three, two-
搞定
Got it.
好样的
Yes!
不可思议 你真行
I can't believe I did it. You kicked ass!
漂亮
Awesome.
好的 伙计们 马上好 好的 放轻松
All right, guys. One sec. Okay. Keep it loose.
准备好了? 开始
You ready? Go.
好热啊
Whew. It is hot out here.
我们还是等下再抓鱼吧
You know what? I think we can fish later.
不要停
We are rolling.
我觉得我该先凉快下
l think I need to, uh, cool off.
那么…
So...
你想…湿身吗?
do you want to get, uh, wet?
你在干什么? M 搞什么鬼?
What are you doing? M.! What the fuck?
我光着身子站在这 这个木头人就这么…一动不动
l am standing here giving it my all, and this jock is just...standing there..
停 怎么回事?
Cut! Hey, what's goin' on, man?
大哥 我在试着给你们俩制造火花
Look, man, I I want to create chemistry between you two.
懂吗? 你们俩站一起就会让人 想到那些
Okay? You guys are, like, the sex of this thing.
你说你要的是家庭真人秀
Mm-hmm. You said you wanted a family reality show.
性一贯是美国的肮脏小秘密
Well, sex is America's dirty little secret.
在教堂里你不能光明正大地说 但在家里 在电视里…
Huh? You can't talk about it at church, but at home, on TV...
观众喜欢看太阳底下 湿漉漉油光发亮的火辣身材
people wanna see hard bodies wet and glistening in the sun.
我要是这么干 我老妈和六个侄女 就一辈子都不理我了
If I do that, I have a mother and six nieces that will never speak to me again.
老兄 观众就是要找乐子
Look, man, people wanna be entertained.
Elena和我只是顺水推舟
Elena and I are just greasing the wheeIs a little.
顺水推舟 对
Greasin'the wheels. Yeah.
听着 兄弟 我是来比赛的
Well, look, man, I'm here to play the game, okay?
要推自己推
Now you can go grease the wheels.
要抓鱼自己抓
You can try catching some fsh.
我去林子看看有没吃的
I'll see if I can fnd somethin' to eat in the woods.
"顺水推舟" 你们俩…待会再汇合吧
''Grease the wheels.'' You two. What I'll catch y'all later.
待会再汇合吧
Catch y'all later.
这下好 我要个硬汉 谁知是童子军
Great. I wanted Diddy. I got a Boy Scout.
M 等等 我们不需要Jake
M., wait. We don't need Jake.
我不正是你想要的吗
I'm all the sex that you want.
你很正 但这不是一回事 你上哪去?
You're hot, but it's not the same thing. Hey, where are you going?
怎么 你要去拍你女友吗?
What, are you gonna go shoot your girlfriend?
不 说实话我把故事重新安排了下
No. Actually, I've gotta rethink the story lines.
听着 我几乎是无偿出演…
Hey, listen, I'm doing this gig for, like, free...
我要尽可能多地出镜
and I want all the screen time that I can get.
我也知道怎样才能实现
And I know how to make sure that happens.
当真?
Really?
我吃这套
Works for me.
你没听懂
You don't get it.
只要和体育扯上一点关系 我都没辙
I'm, like, a complete spaz when it comes to anything even remotely athletic.
很抱歉刚才我没帮忙
I'm sorry I didn't help.
这是比赛 我明白
You're just playing the game. I understand.
我真的很需要这笔钱
I just really need this money.
如果你担心的是这个 我保证我不会把辐射卡给你的
I'm not gonna give you my radiation card, if that's what you're worried about.
我很高兴真的度过了第一天
I'm just thrilled that I actually get to live another day.
这孙子…
Motherfucker.
我知道这不好受
Look, I know it hurts...
可你根本不需要他
but you don't need a piece of shit like that in your life.
没有他你过得更好
You're better off without him.
我以为他就是真命天子
I thought he was the one. You know? Yeah.
我经常碰见这种混蛋
I've known scumbags like this all my life.
半年前我发现未婚夫和 我最好的朋友上了床
Six months ago, I caught my fance in bed with my best friend.
真的?
Really?
更绝的是…
Top it off-
他把我卡刷爆 害我负债累累
He used my credit cards to put me into major debt.
所以我一定要赢
That's why I have to win this game.
你越早认识到 只能靠自己
The sooner you realize you can only depend on yourself...
你的日子就会过得越好
the better off you'll be.
振作
Come on.
深呼吸 下去把他们教训一顿
Take a breath. Let's go down there and kick his ass.
你有教训你未婚夫吗? 揍进医院了
Is that what you did to your fance? Put him in the hospital.
来
Come on.
不 我还是用自己的方法吧
No. I'll just deal with it in my own way.
他罪有应得
It's what he deserves.
我不是这样的人 走吧
It's not me. Come on.
不 我不像你 我不想成为你
No. I'm not like you. I don't want to be.
对不起 表达错了 没关系
I'm sorry. That came out wrong. It's okay.
来嘛 给我说说你的艳遇 一次也好
Come on.Just tell me one hot experience that you had.
我的天 要是精彩的话我可以送你上霍华德·斯特恩的节目(脱口秀)
Oh, God. I can get you on Howard Stern if it's good.
我有个哥们在他纽约的工作室里干活 你真白痴
I got a buddy who works in the studio in New York. You're such a moron.
但我们是同组 同一个…组
Yeah, but we're on the same team here. You know, the same...team.
好啦 好啦 好啦 我闭嘴 我闭嘴
All right. All right, all right. I'll stop. I'll stop.
我发誓 人格担保 不讲黄段子
I swear. Cross my heart. No more sex talk.
现在起你就是我正儿八经的 同志妹妹 和解好吗?
From now on, you'll be the uptight lesbian sister I never had. Truce?
既然都是一家人了 告诉我 谁先帮谁口交呢?
Oh. And now that we're family, tell me-Who went down on who frst?
奶奶个熊 开玩笑啦 我只是…
.Pendejo...I'm kidding. I'm just-
烧烤?
Is that barbecue?
任务他妈的完成了
Mission fuckin' accomplished.
等等 太简单了 可能是个陷阱
Wait. This is too easy. Maybe this is a trap to make us lose the game.
什么陷阱? 这是猎人营地 老妹
What trap? It's a hunter's camp, sister.
你干什么? 我饿坏了 好他妈香啊
What are you doing? I'm starved, and, damn, that smelIs awesome.
要这真是猎人营地 我们也不能偷别人食物
If this is a real hunter's camp, we can't just steal his food.
为什么不行? 不是"适者生存"吗? 见者有份
Why the hell not? It's a ''survival of the fttest'' kind of thing. Finders, keepers.
你是同志 你的男人气概哪去了?
You're a lesbian. Where are your cojones?
要是我们拿回去分给大家 他们就不会踢我们走
If we bring this back to share with the others, nobody's gonna want us out of the game.
怎么? 烫到了?
Ow! What, it's hot?
终于协调一致了 别得寸进尺
Finally, we're a team. Don't push your luck.
野猪肉
Mmm! Pork.
这些山里人烧烤真有一手
Man, these hillbillies really know their barbecue.
你打算怎么办? 走人
So what are you gonna do? I'm getting outta here.
我打给技师叫他们送我回Wheeling
I'll call the techies to drive me back to Wheeling.
你走错路了 旅行车和手机在那头
You're headed the wrong way. R.V. and cell phones are back that way.
旅行车那边没信号
I can't get a signal from the R.V.
我要去那边打 好吧
I'm just gonna call them from there. Okay.
而且我不想在拖车那里碰见Michael
Besides, I really don't want to run into Michael at the trailer.
开玩笑吧 不要 你疯了
You're kidding. No, you're crazy.
好吧 有人吗?
Okay. Hello?
有人吗?
Hello?
你不能随便走进别人家里
Uh, you can't just walk into somebody's house.
有人吗?
Hello?
我想借用下电话
I need to use your phone, please.
我们不该来这
We shouldn't be here.
那你就在外面等我
Then just wait for me outside.
打完电话我就走
I wanna make one phone call, and I'm gone.
有人吗?
Hello?
好了 没电话 那么…
All right. No phone, so-
可以走了吗?
Uh, we done yet?
真他妈的见鬼
Holy shit.
一家子畸形人
The whole family's deformed.
天 你看这双胞胎
God. Look at the twins.
没事的 别担心
You'll be all right.Just don't worry.
等等 别把拌倒她了
Hold on. Don't drop her.
把她抬桌上
Get her over on the table.
对…对…
There...Yeah...Yeah..
孩子快出来了 你陪着妈妈
Baby's comin'now. You stay here with Ma.
我去找些水来
I'll go and fetch some water.
工具箱
The toolbox!
快走 快走
Go! Go!
锁住了 怎么办?
It's locked! What do we do now?
救命
Help me!
那里有亮光 那里有亮光
There's light! There's light!
推
Push!
唔
Uh..
妈
Ma!
救命
Help me.
他妈的
Fuck.
嗨 你还好吧? 我很好
Hey. You good? I'm good.
你能为我保守这个秘密吗?
Can we, uh, keep this as our secret?
我不想跟Mara闹翻
I wouldn't wanna mess things up with Mara.
我想她就是我的命中人 随便你
You know, I think she's the one. Whatever.
我要回旅行车去了 你来不?
I'm headin' back to the R.V. You comin'?
不去 我已经完成工作了
No. Myjob's done.
我就呆这里 晒晒日光浴
Just gonna stay here and tan.
替我向Mara问好
Tell Mara I say hi.
你会成为主角的
You're the star.
M? 是你吗?
M? Is that you?
别吓闹 不好玩
Don't screw around. It's not cool.
啊他妈的
Aw, shit.
好吧 发生什么事了?
Okay. What's the challenge?
该死的
Fuck!
不要
No!
Mara…
Mara.
嗨 Neil 我回来了 你在干什么 扔骰子呢?
Hey, Neil. I'm back, yo. What, you droppin' a deuce?
说真的 Neil 点个火吧
Seriously, Neil, light a match.
Neil…
Neil.
你不在这呀
Guess you're not here.
好吧 看看都录了些啥
All right. Let's see what we can see.
快跑 不 快跑
Run. No. Run.
怎么搞的?
What?
啊该死的
Aw, fuck.
我来看看
Let's see.
这个…好的 这个也没坏
Well, this-All right. This works.
怎么搞的 Neil
Well, what's the ma Neil.
我找不出故障 好像是好的
I can't fg-This seems fne.
很好 你花钱上电影学校只是为了…
Great. You know, you spend money on flm school just to-
看上去没坏
It looks fine.
输入 输出 好了 有信号了
lnput, output. Yeah, that works.
看起来不错 那是什么? Nina?
Well, looks good. What is that? Nina?
该死的 Neil 车子不能动 连着电源的
Damn it! Neil, can't move! We're hardwired in!
该死…
What the-
太棒了 好吃
This is cool. It's good.
再来一块 唔? 嗯
Going for another one, huh? Mmm.
独一无二的白肉 如果这就是末日战场也让它来吧
The only white meat. If this is what Armageddon's like, bring it on, baby.
是啊也许下次你就得找个围嘴了
Yeah, maybe next time you should search for a bib.
碰上你们两个 太好了
I'm so glad I ran into you guys.
是啊别忘了是谁给你搞来的美食 老兄
Yeah, and don't forget who got you the nosh, dude.
如果你获得处理辐射卡的机会 把卡片给别人 不要给我
You win the chance to get rid of that nuclear card, send it someplace else.
别担心
No worries.
嗨 M和Elena在哪? 哦
Hey, where's M and Elena? Oh.
在河边拍未分级的DVD版
Back at the river shooting the unrated version of the DVD.
等会儿见 哦 伙计
I'll see you two later. Oh, dude.
我走不动了 撑死了 一时半会做不了爱了
I can't even move. I'm so stuffed, sex is gonna have to wait.
打屁精
Shit ghost!
喔…你真下流
Ow...You're nasty.
如果你赢了那些钱 你会怎么花?
If you win, what will you do with the money?
如果我赢了那些钱 我要办场最放肆的海滩晚会
When I win, I'm gonna throw the most outrageous beach party in history.
你真老套 你呢?
You're a cliche, dude. How about you?
如果我拿了那笔钱 我想拿个体育医学的学位
Well, when I win, I plan on getting my degree in sports medicine.
自从我胳膊受伤不能打橄榄球了 我发现我还可以帮助其他人
Since my arm won't let me play football anymore, I fgure I can still help others.
永不言弃
You know, stay in the game.
当不了橄榄球英雄 你也想成为其他方面的英雄
Can't be a football hero, so you'll settle for a hero of any kind.
是啊差不多吧
Yeah, somethin' like that.
看来不是所有人都无可救药
Nice to know there's still hope for mankind.
老兄 如果你这样说是为了上她 那你就别妄想了
Dude, if you're sayin' this to get in her pants, forget about it.
她不吃这一套的 住嘴 你呢?
She doesn't play on our team. Shut up. How about you?
你打算怎么花那笔钱?
What you plan on doin' with the cash?
我欠我老爸一大笔钱
I owe my father a bunch of money.
有了钱 我就与他脱离关系永远自由了 你老爸?
If I win, I am free and clear of him for good. Your father?
他不赞成我的生活方式
He doesn't approve of my lifestyle.
想跟我划清界线
Wants nothing to do with me.
唔 我猜你和家人格格不入
Hmm. I guess you can't choose family.
老兄 M 头都大了
Man, M is so screwed.
他想拍一部中美剧集 但却雇了个同性恋…
He wanted a show for Middle America, but he hired a lesbo...
敏感的运动员 狂躁的素食者…
a sensitivejock, a bipolar vegan...
极端糊涂虫和好莱坞小姐
an extreme fuck-up and Miss Hollywood.
老兄 我们简直是地狱版的"红色国度"
Dude, we're the red-state cast from hell.
哦 天哪 我的天哪
Oh, God! Oh, God!
呀 Nina
Yo, Nina.
你没事吧 Nina? Mara…死了
You all right, Nina? Mara's...dead.
发生什么事了? 我们得离开这里 马上
What happened to you? We have to get out of here now.
你说什么? 他们杀了她
What? They killed her!
嗨 听着 冷静点 他们会找到我们的
Hey, look. Calm down. They'll fnd us here!
深吸口气 谁会找到我们的? 你在说什么?
Take a deep breath. Who will fnd us here? What are you talkin' about?
那些山里的怪物 他们把Mara杀了…
These hillbilly freaks! They killed Mara...
把她绑在卡车头上
and they tied her to the hood of their truck!
我们得离开这里 马上…
We have to get out ofhere right now..
太精彩了 你怎么了?
This is awesome! What is wrong with you?
我是说真的 得了 这也是游戏的一部分
I'm not kidding! Come on. It's part of the game.
后末日疯子在树林里晃荡 这不是游戏 好吗?
Post-apocalyptic crazies roaming through the forest. It's not a game, okay?
那些山里人吃了她的手指
These hillbillies were eating her fnger!
山里人吃人 M 真是个天才
Hillbilly cannibals. M is a genius.
不要笑了 不要笑了 老兄 好吗? 别笑了
Stop laughing! Yo, stop laughing, man, okay? Hold on.
是Mara 她是M的女朋友 她是剧情安排的一部分 我明白
It's Mara. She's M's girlfriend. She was in on it. I got this.
你看到的是特效
What you saw was special effects.
我看到的都是真的
What I saw was real!
我们得马上离开这里
We need to get out of here now!
求求你了 好 好 好 我们走
Please. Yeah. Yeah, yeah. We're going.
这只是测试我们会不会逃跑
This is just a test to see if we bug out.
这种片子总是对手之间相互吓唬
These kind of shows always screw with their contestants.
你们要走就走吧 我要留下来 赢那十万美金
You guys wanna go, go ahead. I'm stayin' put and winnin' the hundred G's.
他们也会杀了你的 老兄
Then they'll kill you too, man.
怎么了?
What?
不
No!
Nina? Nina…
Nina? Nina..
真他妈的…那…那是Kimberly的纹身
Get the fuck That-That's Kimberly's tattoo.
该死的 那是她的腿
Holy shit. That's her leg.
是的 游戏结束了 Amber 我们走吧
That's it. Game's over. Amber, let's go.
快走
Come on.
Jonesy…
Jonesy!
他们是吃人族 老兄 住嘴
They're fucking cannibals, dude. Shut up.
旅行车究竟在哪里? 就在山脊那边
Where the hell's the R.V.? Just over the ridge.
不要说话 赶路吧 我在赶呢
Keep quiet and keep moving. I ain't stoppin'.
我的脚
My foot!
让我看看 我是跑路专家 得继续跑 否则会死
Let me look at it. I'm a shark, man. I gotta keep moving, or I die.
你他妈的住嘴 你们先去旅行车
Shut the fuck up. You guys get to the R. V.
我们就跟上
We'll be right behind you.
会很痛的 他妈的
This is gonna suck. Oh, shit!
我得把伤口压住
I need to put pressure on that.
快点 把护腕给我 不
Come on. Give me your wristband. No!
听着 不要再遮遮掩掩了
Look, you don't have to hide anymore.
你怎么知道的?
How'd you know?
当我发现我再也不能打橄榄球时 我也干过同样的事
When I found out I'd never play football again, I spiraled down pretty hard.
医生让我参加她的自杀病人小组
My therapist told me I should sit in one of her suicide support groups.
为了让我对人生有个更好的认识
You know, give me a better perspective.
曾有个女孩也跟你这样 只是她用的是大手帕
There was a girl that used to do the same thing, only she used a bandana.
这疤什么时候有的? 六个月前
So how old is the scar? About six months.
怎么回事?
What happened?
在我一生中…我相信了太多的坏人
I just trusted too many of the wrong people...all my life.
但我现在挺过来了 那这是旧事重提了?
But I'm past it now. So it's old news?
你觉得我来赢那笔钱是为了什么?
Why do you think I came to win this game?
估计你会有机会得到那笔钱的
Guess you'll get your chance to do just that.
你要敢放个屁 老东西 我就崩了你
You so much as fart, old man, and I'll drop you.
不要杀我 老兄 我是虔诚的基督教徒
Don't kill me, brother. I'm a good Christian man.
该死的 你确定是这里? 是啊就是这里
Shit. Are you sure? Yeah. This was the place.
这有轮胎印空的设备箱 还有垃圾
Here are the tire tracks, the empty equipment cases, the garbage.
真他妈祸不单行
This is so f'ed in the A.
他妈的旅行车不见了 那我们继续走吧
The fucking R.V. is gone! Let's just keep going!
我们死定了 去哪? 最近的小镇也在50英里以外
We're dead meat. Where to? The nearest town is 50 miles away.
我们最终会被山里人拿来做烧烤的
We're all gonna end up hillbilly barbecue.
最后一次警告 保持安静 走吧
I'm not gonna tell you again. Keep quiet! Just come on.
主干道旁有个老造纸厂 已经废弃了
There's that old paper mill out by the main road. It's abandoned.
我们得找个地方躲起来 也许那会有个公用电话
We gotta dig in somewhere. Maybe there's a public phone.
你知道为什么说是废弃的吗? 是因为里面什么也没有 包括电话
Dude, you know why they call it abandoned? 'Cause there's nothing in it, including phones!
嗨 不要伤害我
Hey! Don't hurt me!
那是捕熊夹 这里没有动物
That's a bear trap. There's no animaIs around here.
他们为什么要放个捕熊夹?
Why do they have a fucking bear trap set?
他们不是要捉熊 是捉人
They're not trapping bears. They're trapping people.
这里没有野味吃 他们就吃我们
There's no wildlife to eat around here. They're eating us.
好吧 我错了 去纸浆厂是个好主意 我们赶紧离开这里
Okay, I was wrong. Paper mill's a great idea. Let's just get outta here.
不 不 不 听着 老兄 如果我们走那条路 我们就死定了
No, no, no. Look, man, if we take the road, we're sitting ducks, all right?
所以我希望大家一起行动 当心脚下
So I want everyone to stick together and watch where you step.
对
Yeah, no shit.
好啊
Yeah.
你炸了谁 老家伙?
Who you blowin' up, old-timer?
哦 是鳟鱼
Oh,just the trout.
只有这样 他们才会浮到水面
Only way to bring 'em to the surface.
炸药把它们震昏
Dynamite stuns 'em.
然后它们就像睡莲一样浮上来 我再捞出来
Then they float like lily pads, and I just scoop 'em up.
你老婆很美
Pretty wife.
是的 那是我的黛利拉 她给了今生我最美好的时光
Yeah, that's my Delilah. Gave me the happiest days of my life.
上帝保佑她
God bless her soul.
你这幸运的混蛋
You know, you one lucky son of a bitch.
很多人进了树林 就没见他们出来过
Lotta folk go in them woods. Never seen one come out.
我都没有和他们有过接触
l stay clear of them myself.
这里有多少这样的怪胎?
How many of those freaks are out there?
不清楚 比你碰到的多 这是肯定的
Hard to know. More than the ones you run across. That's for sure.
他们是什么?
What are they?
老兄 其实跟你我都一样 只是丑一点…
Oh,just like you and me, brother, 'cept uglier...
更强壮一点
and a lot stronger.
嗨 我曾经开车撞到他们的一个小孩
Hey, I hit one of them young'uns once in my pickup.
他马上跳起来 然后继续前行
He popped up and just kept goin'.
是化学物质让他们发生了变异
It's the chemicaIs changed 'em.
纸浆厂约30年前关闭了…
Pulp mill shut down near 30 years ago...
留下一片狼藉
and left a mess.
所有野兽都因毒物而灭绝了
And the poison killed off all the game.
这附近的居民大部分都搬走了
Most folks 'round these parts left.
有一户人家留了下来…
There's one family that stayed on in this holler...
不久 妈妈生了很多宝宝…
and pretty soon their babies started gushin' out of their mama's womb...
跟我放外面的鳟鱼一样丑
just as ugly as them trout I got hangin' out there.
宝宝们长大了 有了自己的孩子
And then they grow up, have kids of their own.
结果生出来的孩子更丑
Turned out even worse.
你要留下来吃点鱼吗?
You gonna stay for a bite?
鱼很难看 但煎起来很好吃
Fish is ugly, but they fry up real good.
不 非常感谢 但我得走了
No. Much obliged, but I gotta get goin'.
好吧 如果你要去救你朋友 去算账…
Well, if you're gonna head out to get your friends, settle the score...
最好天黑前出来
best jump to it before it gets dark.
你是不会想晚上呆在树林里的
You don't wanna be out in them woods at night.
你为什么要留下来 老人家?
Why do you stay, old-timer?
我永远都不能离开这里
Well, I could never leave.
我得跟我孩子在一起
Gotta stay close to my young'uns.
操你妈的…我要杀了你
You motherfucker...l gonna kill you, man..
你杀了我的孩子
You killed my boy!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
我要杀了你…我要杀了你 混蛋
I'll kill you...I'll kill you, motherfucker..
我要杀了你
I'll kill you!
操你妈的 我肯定要杀了你
Motherfucker! I'm sure 'nough gonna kill you!
我要抓到你…我要教你怎么跟我的孩子打交道
I'll get you...I'll teach you to mess with my kids..
代我向尊夫人问好
Say hello to the missus for me.
这就是他们其中一个
It's one of them.
是Elena 是吗? 为什么这么认为?
It's Elena. Yeah? What makes you think that?
嗨
Hey!
放开她
Get off her!
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
Nina 等等
Nina, wait!
他妈的
Oh, shit.
快跑…快跑
Come on...Come on..
救命
Help me!
Help!
Nina在哪? 她丢下我们跑了
Where's Nina? She deserted us.
混蛋 继续赶路
Son of a bitch! Just keep moving.
听着 我们分头行动 我去找Nina
Look, split up. I'll fnd Nina.
我们在造纸厂碰头 走 好的
We'll meet up at the mill. Go! Okay.
Nina 救命…救命
Nina! Help me...Help me..
Nina? 救命
Nina? Help me..
Nina? 我…在洞里
Nina? I'm...down here.
Nina? 你没事吧?
Nina? Are you okay?
我们得救你出来 好吗?
We gotta get you out of there, all right?
听着 抓着我的手 抓着 Nina
Look, come on. Come on, Nina.
我够不到
I can't reach.
抓着我的手 Nina
Come on, Nina!
快够到了
Almost.
好了 坚持住
Okay, hold on.
我抓到你了 我抓到你了
I've got you now. I've got you.
稍微往右一点…
Try a little right
怎么了?
What happened?
我的肩膀 脱臼了 你得帮我接上
It's my shoulder. It's dislocated. You gotta help me pop it in.
啊不 Nina 轻点儿 好了 拉一下再扭一下 明白吗?
Ah, no, Nina! Easy! Okay, pull and twist, okay?
来吧
Go.
扶我起来 Nina
Help me up. Nina.
好像去打仗一样
It's like going to war.
Amber,Jonesy 都没事吗? 我们都没事
Amber,Jonesy Did they make it? We all made it.
我们去造纸厂跟他们会合 好吗?
We'll meet up with them at the mill, okay?
走吧 走吧 走了
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go!
快点 Nina
Come on, Nina.
走吧 去哪?
Let's go. Where?
该死 该死 该死
Shit! Shit! Shit!
你…你刚才狠狠教训了他们
You-You totally kicked ass back there.
我说真的 你就像战士公主西娜
I'm serious. You were, like, Xena, Warrior Princess.
你说得对 我以前就是个彻彻底底的混蛋
You were right. I was a total asshole before.
我再也不会贬低你或其他女人了
I'm never gonna dis you or any other female ever again.
很好 太棒了 我们甩掉他们了
Great. It's cool. We outran 'em.
快跑
Run.
啊 啊
Ow! Ow!
快点
Come on.
哦 该死 快跑
Oh, shit. Come on!
好了
Just-There.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God!
Jonesy 救救我 救救我
Jonesy! Help me! Help me!
Amber Amber 救救我
Amber! Amber, help me!
Jonesy 放我下来 放我下来 不
Jonesy! Get me down! Get me down! Oh, no! Oh!
Amber Amber 救救我
Amber! Amber, help me!
主啊哦哦 上帝 快点 Amber
Christ...Oh...Oh, God...Hurry, Amber..
他来了 他来…
He's coming! He's com-
Amber? Amber 快跑 不
Amber? Amber, go! No!
Amber 不要 快跑 我不会丢下你的
Amber, don't do this! Get away! I'm not leaving you!
快跑 快跑 不要 Amber 不要
Go! Run! No! Amber, no!
哦 天哪…哦 天哪
Oh, God...Oh, God..
Amber…
Amber?
Jonesy…
Jonesy!
Jonesy..
抓住我的手
Give me your hand..
嗯?
Huh?
不要看下面
Don't look down.
我在这儿
I'm here.
Amber 我很怕
Amber, I'm scared.
还有我呢
You're not alone.
好吧 我要救我们俩离开这里
All right. I'm gonna get us out of here.
我妈妈以前老说我会长命…
You know, my mother always used to say I'd live forev-
就是那 Jonesy没瞎说
There it is. Jonesy wasn't kidding.
这个地方荒废了
This place is dead.
"天生缺陷" 不假
''Birth defects.'' No shit.
什么都看不到 我们到底怎样才能找到他们?
Can't see anything. How the hell are we gonna fnd 'em in here?
那就让Amber和Jonesy来找我们吧
Let Amber and Jonesy fnd us.
你从哪弄来的? 为比赛准备的
Where'd you get that? I brought it with me for the game.
我想这可能会派上用场这是舞弊
I thought it might come in handy. That's cheating.
告发我啊
Sue me.
你觉得他们在上面吗? 也许他们找了个短波收音机呼救
You think they're up there? Maybe they found a C.B. radio, called for help.
我先走
I guess I'll go frst.
小心点
Be careful.
他们应该就在附近
They gotta be around here somewhere.
如果他们到了这里
If they even made it here at all.
快出现 伙计们 你们在哪?
Come on, guys. Where you at?
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
那只是个小女孩 看起来她在这里很久了
She was just a little girl. Looks like she's been in there forever.
她在躲着 是的 但是躲谁呢?
She's hiding. Yeah, but from whom?
不对劲
This isn't right.
Nina 不要 Nina 不 Nina
Nina, no! Nina! No, Nina!
太晚了 我们得马上离开这里 不 不 Nina
Too late! We've gotta get out of here now! No! No, Nina!
我们不能丢下他们 明白吗? 走吧
We cannot leave them, okay? Let's go.
看 旅行车 我没看到他们
Look, there's the R.V. I don't see 'em.
哦 上帝 这家人干这些勾当已经上十年了
Oh,Jesus. This family's been doing this for decades.
哦 天哪…听起来是M在叫
Oh, my God...That sounds like M screaming.
好吧 我下去看看
Okay, I'm going down there.
不 不 不 不 拿着这个
No, no, no, no. Hold this.
该死 你掩护我
Shit. You got my back?
有人吗… 救命啊… M? M?
Somebody... Please... M? M?
来吧 来吧 来吧…该死的
Come on. Come on. Come on...Fuck..
丑八怪 M…
Fuck face! M...
他妈的让我出去
Get me the fuck out of here!
他妈的 让我…
Fuck! Get me the fuck
M? 他妈的放我出去
M? Get me the fuck out!
求求你救救我 上帝 救命 求求你们不要
Help me, please! God, help! Please don't!
M? 求求
M? Please...
哦…M…Nina 这是个陷阱
Oh...M...Nina, it's a trap..
该死的
Oh, shit!
Shit.
你们的道德腐化了吗?
Do you have moral rottenness?
兄弟姐妹们 你们必须认识到…
Brothers and sisters, you must know...
我们生活在科技的世界里
that we live in a world of technology.
…参与业余的性行为…
...engaging in extracurricular sexuality...
同性性行为
homosexuality.
不
No!
你选择去天堂还是地狱?
Will it be heaven or hell that you decide on?
这是个十叉路口-
This is the crossroad
你要选择去天堂的岔路吗…
Do you take the turn for heaven...
还是选错了岔路 去到地狱?
or do you take the wrong turn to hell?
这是你寻找道路所需的东西
It's what you need to find your way.
这是你寻找光明所需的东西
It's what you need to find that light.
远离黑暗 不要选错岔路
Stay away from the darkness. Do not take a wrong turn-
…过着充满罪恶或自我毁灭的生活-
...to living a life of sin, of personal destruction-
我有本书能拯救你的生命-
Here I have the book that will save your life-
充满罪恶的生活只会导致…
Living a life of sin will only lead-
操你妈的
Fuck you!
不要…别碰她
Don't do it...Leave her alone..
别碰她 别碰她
Leave her alone! Leave her alone!
不要折磨她了
Stop messing with her!
住手
Stop it.
他妈的你们这些人发什么神经?
What the fuck is wrong with you people?
阿门
Amen.
噎死你们
I hope you fucking choke!
别碰她
Leave her alone!
求求你们了 放我们走吧
Please! Let us go!
快啊救命 救命
Come on, man. Help! Help.
救命 救命 救命
Help. Help. Help.
求你们了 放我们走吧…放我们走吧
Come on. Let us go...Let us go..
放我们走吧…Nina
Let us go...Nina..
救命 救命
Help! Help!
救命…拜托…我们在里面…我们被困住了
Help...Please...We're in here...We're trapped..
求你了 救救我们 救救我们
Please, someone, help us! Help us!
该死的
Fuck!
求你救救我们…我们在里面
Please help us...We're in here..
该死的…别走
Damn it...Don't leave..
救救我们…请救救我们
Help us...Please help us..
请救救我们…请救救我们
Please help us...Please help us..
往这边
This way.
Nina Nina…
Nina! Nina!
Nina…快醒醒 快醒醒
Nina...Come on. Wake up.
Nina 醒醒…Nina…
Nina, wake up...Nina..
你能把手抽出来吗?
Can you pull your hands free?
我要你把手抽出来
I need you to pull your hands free.
我做不到
I can't.
Nina 你得试试…Nina
Nina,you've gotta try...Nina..
Nina 醒醒 Nina 嘘
Nina, wake up! Nina! Shh.
Dale? 不要说话
Dale? Be quiet.
我得这么做 深呼吸然后把手抽出来
I gotta do this. Breathe through it.
准备好了吗? 好了吗? 手抽出来
Ready? Okay? Go.
嘘 嘘
Shh. Shh.
还有一只手
One more.
手抽出来
Go.
站起来
Get up.
那边有个出口
There's an exit door through there.
我们马上就来
We are right behind you.
快去
Go!
Dale…
Dale.
我要你去找Nina
I want you to go fnd Nina.
Dale…嗨 嗨
Dale...Hey! Hey!
去找Nina 快去 我明白了 快去
Find Nina. Go. I've got it. Go!
你就这么点能耐吗 畜牲?
Is that all you got, bitch?
操你妈的
Fuck you!
不 不
No! No!
放开我 你这畜牲 放开我
Let go of me, you son of a bitch! Let go of me!
放开…放开我
Let go...Let go of me..
放开我…该死的
Let go of me...Shit!
放开我 你这畜牲
Let go of me, you son of a bitch!
不 不
No! No!
不要
No!
快
Come on!
其实你不用回来救我的 你知道吗?
You know you didn't have to come back for me, right?
有本事告我啊
Sue me.
哇
Wow.
这车很漂亮
Nice ride.
想不想开车兜兜风吗?
You wanna take it for a spin?
为什么不? 这是这家混蛋给我们 最小的补偿了
Why not? It's the least this fucked-up family owes us.
唔 唔
Mmm. Mmm.